{"quizName":"ERP Chapter 4","questions":[{"question":"Which one of the following is NOT a type of organizational data relevant to the production process?","options":["Company code","Credit control area","Client","Storage location","Plant"],"answerIndex":1},{"question":"In process industries like chemicals and beverages, the bill of materials is also known as a(n)","options":["Formula","List of chemicals","Bill of chemicals","Equation","Material list"],"answerIndex":0},{"question":"Which one of the following best describes a work center?","options":["A location where materials are placed right before they are shipped","Another term used to describe an office building","A location where value-added work needed to produce a material is carried out","A shipping dock","A storage shelf in a warehouse"],"answerIndex":2},{"question":"All of the following can serve as a work center except","options":["A group of machines","A group of people responsible for completing operations","A production line","A work area","A shipping dock"],"answerIndex":4},{"question":"What term describes two simultaneous series of operations needed to build components for a finished product?","options":["Parallel sequences","Alternate sequences","Same sequence","Line sequence","Production sequence"],"answerIndex":0},{"question":"Which one of the following best defines material staging?","options":["Component materials are moved into storage","Component materials are received from the vendor","Component materials are moved from storage and prepared for use","Defective returned goods are broken down into several components for refurbishment","Finished materials are moved back into a storage area"],"answerIndex":2},{"question":"What term identifies the list of materials needed to produce one or more units of a finished good?","options":["Routing","Source materials","Component listing","Bill of components","Bill of materials"],"answerIndex":4},{"question":"At what level are material requirements planning (MRP) and work scheduling data defined?","options":["Client level","Plant level","Company code level","Sales area level","Production level"],"answerIndex":1},{"question":"Which of the following is not a step in the production process?","options":["Production authorization","Goods issue","Request production","Billing","Order release"],"answerIndex":3},{"question":"If a company has adopted the make-to-stock strategy, what is the trigger for the production of goods?","options":["Need to increase inventory","Customer order","Request for quotation","Customer inquiry","Billing document"],"answerIndex":0},{"question":"Which of the following does a routing identify on a production order?","options":["The materials or components to be used in production","The location where operations are to be performed","The capacity requirements of the production order","The location of raw materials in the warehouse","The operations needed to produce a material"],"answerIndex":4},{"question":"What step in the production process is used to enter data in to the SAP ERP system when the operations needed to produce a materials are completed?","options":["Production note","Confirmation","Order complete","Production record","Production outcome"],"answerIndex":1},{"question":"The creation of a production order results in several outcomes including all of the following except","options":["Scheduling","Availability checks","Purchase requisitions","Preliminary costing","Confirmation"],"answerIndex":4},{"question":"What operation in the routing is sometimes necessary to prepare materials for use in production?","options":["Backflushing","Confirmation","Material staging","Recall","Reservation"],"answerIndex":2},{"question":"Which of the following is not an outcome of a goods issue to a production order?","options":["The material master is updated to reflect the reduction in the quantity and value of the materials issued","Actual costs associated with material consumption are calculated","Material reservations are updated","A goods receipt is automatically recorded","An FI document is created to record financial accounting data"],"answerIndex":3},{"question":"When the finished goods have been produced the SAP ERP system allows a user to record which of the following?","options":["Confirmation","Goods issue","Order release","Goods receipt","Authorize production r"],"answerIndex":0},{"question":"Which of the following is an important report in the production process?","options":["Work list","Stock requirement list","Online list","BOM","None of the above"],"answerIndex":1},{"question":"A bill of materials identifies the finished goods that are to be shipped to a specific customer.","options":["True","False"],"answerIndex":1},{"question":"An active bill of materials can be used in the production of a material, but an inactive BOM cannot.","options":["True","False"],"answerIndex":0},{"question":"A work center is a location where materials are placed immediately before they are shipped.","options":["True","False"],"answerIndex":1},{"question":"All operations must be performed in some type of sequence, and many operations can be completed in a variety of sequences.","options":["True","False"],"answerIndex":0},{"question":"Fixed time elements represent the time needed to produce one unit of material.","options":["True","False"],"answerIndex":1},{"question":"Variable time elements are independent of how many units of material are produced.","options":["True","False"],"answerIndex":1},{"question":"Material staging is the process in which component materials are moved from storage and prepared for use.","options":["True","False"],"answerIndex":0},{"question":"Component assignment is a technique that assigns components in a BOM either to a routing or to a specific operation within the routing.","options":["True","False"],"answerIndex":0},{"question":"Production resource tools are movable resources that are shared among different work centers.","options":["True","False"],"answerIndex":0},{"question":"Typically a production order does not include any references to the BOM, routing, or work centers.","options":["True","False"],"answerIndex":1},{"question":"Capacity split is a strategy that is used to determine how the production work  is to be distributed among machines and/or people","options":["True","False"],"answerIndex":0},{"question":"After production has been completed, a goods receipt against the production order is used to pick the goods and ship them to the customer","options":["True","False"],"answerIndex":1},{"question":"If the bill of materials and the routing data are changed after the production order has been created, the system must be manually instructed to reenter the data","options":["True","False"],"answerIndex":0},{"question":"A time ticket is used to record the amount of time required to complete various operations","options":["True","False"],"answerIndex":0},{"question":"Material staging is a technique that is used to automatically record the goods issue when an order is confirmed","options":["True","False"],"answerIndex":1},{"question":"Periodic processing is also known as period-end closing","options":["True","False"],"answerIndex":0},{"question":"Overhead allocation, work in process determination, and order settlement are all included in periodic processing","options":["True","False"],"answerIndex":0},{"question":"A technically complete status for a production order means that even though the main  material is complete, other production processes may be needed to complete smaller components of the material","options":["True","False"],"answerIndex":1}]}